

PROFILE

20 year's Experience as CTO, ICT Manager, Software Analyzer, DevOps and Network Administrator.
Skilled with Scrum, XP, Agile.
Good experience with SQL and NoSQL, ProxySQL, IIS, Nginx, Apache, HAProxy.
Skilled with Linux Servers such as CentOS, Ubuntu, ... also Docker, Docker Swarm, K8s, ESXi, OWASP.
Programming Language with PHP, Python, JavaScript's.
Skilled on concept of OOP, SOA, MVC.
Skilled with ERP systems like SAP, Oracle E-Business Suite.

CONTACT

PHONE: +989127789404

WEBSITE:

https://alidev.pro

EMAIL:

Ali.yousefzadeh@gmail.com

LinkedIn:

https://bit.ly/3fuPnn6

HOBBIES

Chess Literature Linux Swimming

ALI YOUSEFZADEH

CTO, DevOps, Sysadmin

EDUCATION

Apply Mathematics in Computer at Tehran Polytechnic University 1994 - 1998

Main Course I loved was: Statistical, Advanced Programming, Computational Theory, Abstract Algebra, Differential Equations

WORK EXPERIENCE

Free Lancer - Technical Product Manager and DevOps

Jul 2019-Now

Mahan VoIP Co: Auto Call Dialer, Call Center System HoshmandRisk Co: Mutual fund, Brokerage, Portfolio, Risk Management Varlee Co: Stores and wallets Management system

Nesko Inc. - DevOps

Sep 2018-Jul 2019

transportation ecosystem that connects passenger to a network of taxi companies for Canadian company in south of America.

Carpino and Carboy Co - CTO

Jun 2016–Sep 2018 Carpino is Intelligent taxi system Carboy is Intelligent on-site car service system

TANA Co - CTO and Sysadmin

Jul 2013-Jun 2016

Tehran UNICEF App, website for UNHabitat, Kids Learning app, ...

SKILLS

